const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which of the following mythological creatures breathes fire?',
        answers: [
            'A: Unicorn',
            'B: Centaur',
            'C: Dragon',
            'D: High-school principal'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'C: Dragon',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these phrases is often used to describe a trusted aide?',
        answers: [
            'A: Right-hand man',
            'B: Left-leg lady',
            'C: Torso buddy',
            'D: Left-eye lopes'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A: Right-hand man',
    },
    {
        question: 'A sauna is a room that people generally visit to do what?',
        answers: [
            'A: Sleep',
            'B: Sweat',
            'C: Eat',
            'D: Fall in love'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'B: Sweat',
    },
    {
        question: 'In medieval times, which of these professionals was responsible for entertaining the royal courts?',
        answers: [
            'A: Barber',
            'B: Knight',
            'C: Jester',
            'D: Blacksmith'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'C: Jester',
    },
    {
        question: 'For over 50 years, what treat was traditionally included in packs of baseball trading cards?',
        answers: [
            'A: Chocolate wafer',
            'B: Gummi bear',
            'C: Mint stick',
            'D: Bubblegum'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'D: Bubblegum',
    },
    {
        question: 'A parasol is a lightweight form of what accessory?',
        answers: [
            'A: Umbrella',
            'B: Hat',
            'C: Cane',
            'D: Bracelet'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A: Umbrella',
    },
    {
        question: 'Seaweed is a form of what?',
        answers: [
            'A: Bacteria',
            'B: Algae',
            'C: Fungus',
            'D: Sea urchin'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'B: Algae',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was the leader of the band on the TV series Sha Na Na?',
        answers: [
            'A: Benson',
            'B: Bosley',
            'C: Bowzer',
            'D: Baba-Booey'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'C: Bowzer',
    },
    {
        question: 'At the time of his election, who was the oldest person to become President of the United States?',
        answers: [
            'A: George Washington',
            'B: Herbert Hoover',
            'C: Woodrow Wilson',
            'D: Ronald Reagan'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'D: Ronald Reagan',
    },
    {
        question: 'The Pecos River is a major tributary of what U.S. river?',
        answers: [
            'A: Rio Grande',
            'B: Platte',
            'C: Snake',
            'D: Colorado'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A: Rio Grande',
    },
    {
        question: `In the 2000 movie Gladiator, Russell Crowe's character is a gladiator under what Roman emperor?`,
        answers: [
            'A: Titus',
            'B: Commodus',
            'C: Nero',
            'D: Claudius'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'B: Commodus',
    },
    {
        question: 'In 1911, what did explorer Hiram Bingham discover between two peaks in the Andes mountains?',
        answers: [
            'A: City of Machu Picchu',
            'B: Frozen woolly mammoth',
            'C: Lake Titicaca',
            'D: Meteorite from Mars'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A: City of Machu Picchu',
    },
    {
        question: `What 1953 novel marked the first appearance of Ian Fleming's agent James Bond?`,
        answers: [
            'A: Doctor No',
            'B: Goldfinger',
            'C: Casino Royale',
            'D: Live and Let Die '           
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'C: Casino Royale',
    },
    {
        question: 'When three celestial bodies form a straight line, what is it called?',
        answers: [
            'A: Simoom',
            'B: Syzygy',
            'C: String theory',
            'D: Saprobity'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'B: Syzygy',
    },
    {
        question: 'What letter must appear at the beginning of the registration number of all non-military aircraft in the U.S.?',
        answers: [
            'A: N',
            'B: A',
            'C: U',
            'D: L'           
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A: N',
    }
];